MOHAMED RHALLAB

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

www.medrhallab.com



www.medrhallab.com



(581) 999-0687



rhallab.dev@gmail.com



Quebec City, Qc, Canada



www.github.com/marhallab

SKILLS

- HTML
- JavaScript
- Vue.js (2/3)
- Nuxt.js
- ____
- Typescript
- React.js
- jQuery
- REST APIs
- Jira

- CSS
- Sass
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- Git
- SEO
- Scrum
- Wordpress

EDUCATION

DEC IN WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

College limoilou

2018 - 2021

BAC IN MATHEMATICAL SCIENCES

Pythagore High School

2015 - 2018

PROFILE

I am a Front-End developer who has a lot of experience in building interactive and responsive websites and web applications. I specialize mainly in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Vue.js. I also have experience with other JS frameworks and other programming languages!

EXPERIENCES

MAIN FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Insurance Journal (JDA) French Portal English Portal

May 2022 - Present

- Maintaining a microservice front-end architecture that supports a business modal inspired by SAAS.
- · Replace the current Front-end techno from Django to Vue.js
- · Create a new subscription payment flow using Stripe
- Create a new dynamic event app manager, to create new company event pages
- Build new functionalities and improve current ones for a better user experience

VUEJS FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Boite Beet Alfred CRH Canada

October 2021 - April 2022

- Led the front-end of medium to big web projects for renowned clients in QC & Canada
- Use of WordPress headless CMS & Nova CMS for content integration with Vue.js
- Create new reusable components for the UI-Kit used internally

FRONT-END DEVELOPER / IT PROJECT MANAGER

Freelancing / Consulting

March 2020 - March 2021

- · Compliance with SASS and Front-End standards and conventions
- Led new web projects (as a developer & a project manager) for multiple clients
- Understand the need and pain of the client, and give proper solutions to it
- Translate the design system into code while respecting each visual aspect of it (Responsiveness and Reusability of components)